<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mai Hoang Duc</title>
    <link>https://hoangduc1248.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mai Hoang Duc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 21:02:49 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hoangduc1248.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make a calculation for tax in Japan?</title>
      <link>https://hoangduc1248.github.io/blog/2019-02/how-to-make-a-calculation-for-tax-in-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 21:02:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hoangduc1248.github.io/blog/2019-02/how-to-make-a-calculation-for-tax-in-japan/</guid>
      <description>This is a interesting topic for everyone. It also got my attention on this year. So let learn about the taxes together. First we will have two main taxonomy of taxes. One is for individual and one for corporate and the way it calculate is different. We go to the first part the individual taxes system.
Individual taxes In Japan we have a progressive tax system. The more money you made the more you lose. In other words, with higher income your tax per 100 JPY will higher. So let check it out.
First thing you have to know is that the tax system is five you a 380,000 JPY income as tax-free and they call that living expenses. The tax system will start when your income excess that amount. And if you have dependents you will get 380,000 extra per dependents. After the system will make a taxes calculation base on your income.
The current national income tax rates are:
   Annual income (JPY) (excluded living expenses) Tax rate Tax on minimum     Less than 1,950,000 5%    1,950,000 to 3,300,000 10% 97500   3,300,000 to 6,950,000 20% 427500   6,950,000 to 9,000,000 23% 1817500   9,000,000 to 18,000,000 33% 3887500   18,000,000 to 40,000,000 40% 9827500   More than 40,000,000 45% 9827500    The earned income deduction</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fukuoka&#39;s trip</title>
      <link>https://hoangduc1248.github.io/blog/2018-09/fukuokas-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 16:06:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hoangduc1248.github.io/blog/2018-09/fukuokas-trip/</guid>
      <description>Brief: A first IEEE conference of mine. I will talk about that I think about Fukuoka.
First of all this conference is a must have step to apply for my new scholarship which is called Rotary-Yoneyama. A very nice scholarship not only on amount of money every month, It also good about to have a very success Japanese consultant. Suddenly, this time I want to learn more about tax, and economy and then it will be nice to have this scholarship.
Morning 18 September 2018, I take a bus to go to Niigata, a beautiful nearby city which have a domestic airport. Wow first time go to the Southern of Japan, a bit excited and I thought that: What is waiting for me in Fukuoka? A new journey? I always like to explore and learn a new thing. This is the life we should learn a new thing or just going to die right away.
After two hours in the sky, I arrive to Fukuoka. DO you know what is my first impressive? A big city compare to my living city and very overcrowded, many thing new, my eye feel so excited. As a sense of a animal, look at the Google map I found out that we have a castle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sendai&#39;s trip</title>
      <link>https://hoangduc1248.github.io/blog/2018-09/sendais-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 16:06:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hoangduc1248.github.io/blog/2018-09/sendais-trip/</guid>
      <description>Hello every one! Today I will talk about my very first trip to attend a conference at Tohoku University.
This trip contain of so many first things of mine.
First time to Sendai, JAPAN Sendai is one of the biggest city in Tohoku. This city is totally different from my city which is called Aizu Wakamatsu city (The smallest city of Fukushima).
Me and Hoang (My senior) go there by bus. And when we got there, we have to wait for my professor and Thang (My another senior). At that time, I and Hoang make a friend with an Indian. He is very nice, proactive and he also a developer. He currently works in Tokyo Japan, but he went to Sendai for a trip to meet his friend and then he was waiting for the bus come back to Tokyo. I always like to make a friend from other countries, It was nice to try to practice your English.
Finally, my professor came, he introduced us to a very delicious restaurant under the Sendai station. He said that this is his favorite food in Sendai. After that, we talk about so many things. Every time I talk with my professor I learn well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>