<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2019 on Mai Hoang Duc</title>
    <link>https://hoangduc1248.github.io/blog/2019/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2019 on Mai Hoang Duc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 16:06:40 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hoangduc1248.github.io/blog/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make a calculation for tax in Japan?</title>
      <link>https://hoangduc1248.github.io/blog/2019-02/how-to-make-a-calculation-for-tax-in-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 21:02:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hoangduc1248.github.io/blog/2019-02/how-to-make-a-calculation-for-tax-in-japan/</guid>
      <description>This is a interesting topic for everyone. It also got my attention on this year. So let learn about the taxes together. First we will have two main taxonomy of taxes. One is for individual and one for corporate and the way it calculate is different. We go to the first part the individual taxes system.
Individual taxes In Japan we have a progressive tax system. The more money you made the more you lose. In other words, with higher income your tax per 100 JPY will higher. So let check it out.
First thing you have to know is that the tax system is five you a 380,000 JPY income as tax-free and they call that living expenses. The tax system will start when your income excess that amount. And if you have dependents you will get 380,000 extra per dependents. After the system will make a taxes calculation base on your income.
The current national income tax rates are:
   Annual income (JPY) (excluded living expenses) Tax rate Tax on minimum     Less than 1,950,000 5%    1,950,000 to 3,300,000 10% 97500   3,300,000 to 6,950,000 20% 427500   6,950,000 to 9,000,000 23% 1817500   9,000,000 to 18,000,000 33% 3887500   18,000,000 to 40,000,000 40% 9827500   More than 40,000,000 45% 9827500    The earned income deduction</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>